http://www.ftdflorists.com/privacy

Fresh, Hand-Delivered Flowers Direct from Local FloristsFresh, Hand-Delivered Flowers Direct from Local FloristsSearch FloristsPrivacy & SecurityYour Security and Privacy Are Important to UsThe protection of your privacy are of the utmost importance to FTDflorists.com. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to third parties.General InformationWhen you visit FTDflorists.com, we collect some basic non-identifying information. This specifically includes information regarding your operating system, browser software, and IP (Internet Protocol) address. This information is collected in order to provide you with satisfactory service. We may use the information to detect problems with our server and to administer our Web site.Links to Other Web SitesFTDflorists.com may contain links to other Web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices and content of these third-party Web sites. We urge you to follow safe Internet practices: Do not supply personal information to these Web sites unless you have verified their security and privacy policies.Your ConsentBy visiting our Web site, you consent to the use of your personal information by FTDflorists.com in the manner specified in the privacy policy. We, however, have the option to change, modify, or add to the terms and conditions of the privacy policy at anytime. These changes will be posted on the site to give you notice. Any customer who does not agree to the altered privacy policy has the option to opt-out.
